

Name : Gede Rana Dewadatta

Date of birth: 20 November 1990

Place of birth: Balikpapan

Handphone : 085697410037

Current location: Dalung Permai Blok K3/100,

Badung, Bali

Summary

I have been working in IT professional Industry for more than 5 years with a minimum of 4 years working experience as a Java Developer and 2 years working in management area.

I started my career as Java Web Developer intern. After 2 years working in JAVA language, I got assignment as RPG 3 and RPG-ILE Developer which based on AS/400 for around 1 year. After that I went back to JAVA language until December 2017. From January 2018 until February 2018 I got triple assignment as Business Analyst, System Architecture and also Co-PM.

Since March 2018, I got assignment as Member of Foundation Dept on PJI. On Foundation Dept, I have to decide the technology for every project, creating template and decide how many mandays that will consume for the project.

Since September 2018, after resigned from PJI, i worked as deputy manager who has assignment as *local* software development manager whereare I have to manage timeline of every project and also decide and conduct training technology that will use for each project on Software Development Department at FIRSTWAP INTERNATIONAL since the company has subsidiary on overseas, the manager itself is taking care other people on Software Development Department on overseas instead on Indonesia.

From January 2019 until March 2019, I work on Lentera Edukasi Digital as Software Architecture as well for every IT project they get. On Section Project Experiences, I already declare every project, role and responsibility I worked.

Specific Experience and Skills

Operating Systems Windows, Linux, OS/400,OSX

Database Systems MySQL, Oracle, SQLServer

Skill Category	Skill	Competence Level	
Database:	MySQL	Basic	

	Oracle	 Intermediate
	SQLServer	Intermediate
Computer Languages /	• Java	Intermediate
Script / Frameworks:	Spring Core	 Intermediate
	Spring MVC	Intermediate
	Hibernate	 Intermediate
	JavaScript	 Intermediate
	• JQuery	Intermediate
	AngularJs 1	Basic
	• Struts	Basic
	• RPG 3	Basic
	RPG-ILE	Basic
	• Jasper Report 1.4 With iReport 2.0.5	 Intermediate
	• SSIS	Advance
	Eclipse IDE	Advance
	• PHP	Intermediate
	HTML 4	Basic
	• CSS 2	Basic
	Maven	Advance
	• C#.NET	Advance
	• PHP	 Intermediate
Source Versioning	• SVN	Advance
	• Git	Advance
Operating Systems /	Windows- All flavour	Intermediate
Application Servers:	Linux – CentOS	Advance
	Weblogic 11g	Basic
	Websphere 6.0.2	Basic
	• JBoss 4	Basic
	Apache-Tomcat	 Intermediate
	• OSX	 Advance
	1	

Software Development Waterfall SDLC, Agile/Scrum

Architecture Monolith, Micro-service(s)

Management Project Management, Define KPI for each employee

Formal Education

Bachelor's Degree (S1)

Field of Study : Informatic Engineer

Major : Information Technology

GPA : 2.50

Institution/College : Sanata Dharma University

Graduation : Ungraduated(due to financial issue)

Professional Experiences

1	Project Name	:	Automation for Performance System			
	Company	:	PT Lentera Edukasi Digital			
	Technology	:	Java(Spring+Hibernate) + MySQL			
			Solution Architect			
		:	Analyzing technology environment			
			Analyzing enterprise spesific			
			Analyzing requirements			
	Role & Responsibilities		Controlling Solution Development			
			Setting the collaboration framework			
			Creating Solution Prototype			
			Participating in technology selection			
			Supporting Project Management			
	Client	:	Asuransi Central Asia (ACA)			
	Duration	:	January 2019 – March 2019			
2	Project Name	:	Internal System			
	Company	:	PT FIRSTWAP INTERNATIONAL			
	Technology	:	Java (Spring+Hibernate) + MySQL			
			Deputy Manager of Software Development			
			Manages all the activities of the software development group			
	Role & Responsibilities					
			Sets attainable goals to team members in order for the project			
			to be finished on time			
			Provides guidance to team members to encourage work			
			productivity			

			Makes sure the timeline is followed by the software		
			development group		
			Manages multiple projects at once		
			Ensures appropriate procedures and processes are followed		
			when it comes to software development		
			Represents the software department in meetings		
			Participates in design control activities		
			 Monitors, evaluates and ensures the completion of tasks and projects 		
			Analyze software requirements		
			 Implements design plans, reviews unit tests; documents 		
			software development		
			Monitors status of developing software		
			Writes, reviews and revises product requirements and		
			specifications		
			 Participates in other areas of the software development process 		
			provides technical support to other company personnel		
	Duration	:	September 2018 – December 2018		
3	Project Name	:	CR Avantrade Bank Muamalat		
	Company	:	PT Pradipta Jatis Indonesia		
	Technology	:	Java(Spring+Zkoss) + Oracle 11g		
			Technical Leader/Co-PM/Solution Architech		
			Analyzing technology environment		
	Role & Responsibilities	:	Analyzing enterprise spesific		
			Analyzing requirements		
			Controlling Solution Development		
			Setting the collaboration framework		
			Creating Solution Prototype		
			Participating in technology selection		
			Supporting Project Management		
			Analyzing technology environment		
			Analyzing enterprise spesific		
			Designing, developing and implementing Applications		
	Client	:	PT Jati Piranti Solusindo		
	Duration	:	May 2018 – September 2018		
4	Project Name	:	Enhancement HCMS Phase II		
	Company	:	PT Jati Piranti Solusindo		
	Technology		: Java(Spring + Zkoss) + Oracle 10g		
. —	recimology	<u> </u>			
	Role & Responsibilities		Java Technical Lead / Co-PM		

			Delegating work and assignment work to team member
			Collaborating with Team to identify and fix technical problems
			Creating end goals for the team
	-		Checking that software and applications are update
			Supervising system modifications
			 Conducting security audits to identify areas of improvement
			and the second s
			Guiding the team through technical issues and challenges
	Client	:	Astralife
	Duration	:	January 2018 – February 2018
5	Project Name	:	Dedicated FIFCORE – Order Management Support
	Company	:	PT Jati Piranti Solusindo
	Technology	:	Java (Spring+Zkoss) + Oracle 11g
	0,		Application Support Team Lead
	1		Lead and prioritize the Applications support team's workload
			Develop, co-ordinate and promote the effective functioning of
			problem management activities across all of support teams
			Provide timely and export advice on emerging trends and
			issues affecting Service Delivery and Support. Develop
	Dala 9 Daspansibilities	١.	strategies to allow Application Support to manage resultant
	Role & Responsibilities	:	problems Provide input to the implementation, backup and rell back
			Provide input to the implementation, backup and roll-back plans
			Act as a technical resource for internal and external projects
			Maintain application monitoring, performance tuning and
			testing
			Interact with internal teams and external 3rd party vendors to
			trouble shoot and resolve complex problems
	Client	:	PT. Federal International Finance
	Duration	:	August 2017 – December 2017
6	Project Name	:	HCMS Support
	Company	<u> </u> :	PT Jati Piranti Solusindo
	Technology	:	Java(Spring+Zkoss) + Oracle 10g
			Application Support Team Lead
			Lead and prioritize the Applications support team's workload
			Develop, co-ordinate and promote the effective functioning of
	Role & Responsibilities	:	problem management activities across all of support teams
	,		Provide timely and export advice on emerging trends and
			issues affecting Service Delivery and Support. Develop
			strategies to allow Application Support to manage resultant problems
<u> </u>	<u> </u>		producins

			Provide input to the implementation, backup and roll-back plans	
			Act as a technical resource for internal and external projects	
			Maintain application monitoring, performance tuning and testing	
			 Interact with internal teams and external 3rd party vendors to trouble shoot and resolve complex problems 	
	Client	:	PT. AstraLife and PT. Federal International Finance	
	Duration	:	January 2017 – July 2017	
7	Project Name	:	Dedicated HCMS Support	
	Company	:	PT Jati Piranti Solusindo	
	Technology		Java(Spring+Zkoss) + Oracle 10g	
			Java Application Support Team Lead	
]		Lead and prioritize the Applications support team's workload	
	-		Develop, co-ordinate and promote the effective functioning of	
	Role & Responsibilities	:	problem management activities across all of support teams	
	·		Provide timely and export advice on emerging trends and	
			issues affecting Service Delivery and Support. Develop	
			strategies to allow Application Support to manage resultant problems	
			 Provide input to the implementation, backup and roll-back plans 	
			Act as a technical resource for internal and external project	
			Maintain application monitoring, performance tuning and testing	
			 Interact with internal teams and external 3rd party vendors to trouble shoot and resolve complex problems 	
	Client	:	AstraLife	
	Duration	:	May 2016 – December 2016	
8	Project Name	:	OutSource	
	Company	:	PT Treemas Solusi Utama	
	Technology	:	Java, RPG/400, Javascript Native	
			Java Developer and RPG/400 Developer	
			Developing Core Banking Current Account and Saving Account Module, GL Module, and Deposit Module	
	Role & Responsibilities	:	Developing Migration Core Banking System	
			Supporting Core Banking System	
	1		•	
	Client	:	Telkom Sigma	
	Duration	:	May 2014 – April 2016	
		<u> </u>	, 1	

9	Project Name	:	Internal System
	Company	:	PT Telsis Indonesia
	Technology	:	Java (JSP) + MySQL
	Role & Responsibilities	:	Java Developer
			Develop Timesheet Application System
			Develop SEO
			Develop Mailing Application System
			Develop School Information System
			Develop Budgeting Application System
	Duration	:	July 2013 – January 2014
10	Project Name	:	Library Information System
	Company	:	Widya Wahana Tuka, Bali
	Technology	:	Java(JSP)+MySQL
	Role & Responsibilities	:	Freelance Java Developer
			Develop Library Information System
			Develop Web Company Profile
	Duration	:	May 2010 – July 2010

Training

No		Туре		Cubiant	Time	Remarks
INO	Training	Certificate	Award	Subject	Time	Remarks
1	×		-	Core Banking	2015	Internal
-	^	_		Business Process	2013	Training
2	X		-	Leadership	2016	Internal
	^	_		Leadership	2010	Training
3	×	_		Negatiation	2016	Internal
3	Χ	_	-	Negotiation	2010	Training
4	x	χ -	-	DBA	2016	Internal
4	^	_				Training
5	x	_	_	Decision Making	2014	Internal
3	^	_	-	Decision Making	2014	Training
6	x		_	Problem Solving	2014	Internal
0	^	-	-	Problem Solving	2014	Training
7	x			Building Effective	2014	Internal
′	^	-	-	People	2014	IIICIIIdi
8	_	Х	_	Human Resources	2018	_
0	-		-	Business Process		_